First Name: Jonelle Last Name: Adona

Recent Graduate at University of Central Florida jonelle.adona@knights.ucf.edu

This resume was automatically generated from: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonelle-adona

## **Summary**

I am an upcoming graduate at the University of Central Florida with the intent of earning a Bachelor's degree in Health Administration. I was previously interning in the Human Resources department at a well established hospital based in East Orlando.

I have experience in leadership roles from my university career, and I strive to continue to be a valuable leader in the future. I am passionate about helping others and I strive to give my best work possible to any role that I come across.

I am look for opportunities in any healthcare administrative related positions within the Seattle or Denver area, and I would love to connect with you!

## **Experience**

#### Intern at AdventHealth

January 2020 -

- Created an intern binder to help guide upcoming interns
- Helped with nursing float pool projects
- Answered HR related questions via phone and in person

### **Guest Advocate at Target**

August 2018 - August 2019

## Team Lead / Scheduling at UCF SGA Ticket Center

January 2017 - December 2019

- Made monthly schedules through Microsoft Excet
- Trained new hires

- Provided information about ticket sales and policies to guests

# **Education**

University of Central Florida Health Service Administration , Business Administration and Management, General, 2015 - 2020